

COLLEN KRIEL

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+855 88 738 0135

collen.kriel@gmail.com

Skype: collen.kriel

Twitter: @collenkriel

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/collenkriel

GitHub: github.com/CollenK



I've lived & traveled in SEA for the past two years while working as a freelance tech writer. With a background in software sales and a love of technology, I now want to spend my time creating fun, easy-to-use web experiences.

I am looking to join a dynamic team where I can learn, have fun & contribute to something that doesn't suck.



EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE TECH WRITER

SILICONANGLE MEDIA, INC. | SEP 2014 - PRESENT

- I cover a wide range of breaking technology news
- Create 6 8 resource articles per week on the latest technology
- · Contribute to overall editorial strategy

PARTNER ACCOUNT MANAGER

MIMECAST SOUTH AFRICA | JUN 2013 - FEB 2014

- Managed 15+ channel partners
- Provided sales & marketing support to partner sales
- New channel partner recruitment & training

SENIOR ACCOUNT MANAGER

FIRST DISTRIBUTION | MAR 2011 - MAY 2013

- Managed 25+ IBM Software channel partners
- Provided sales & marketing support across IBM's full stack of Enterprise software solutions
- New channel partner recruitment & training



EDUCATION

CAREERFOUNDRY FULL-STACK ONLINE BOOTCAMP CAREERFOUNDRY, BERLIN | MAY 2016 - PRESENT

CERTIFICATE IN INTERNET MARKETING UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN - ONLINE | 2011

DIPLOMA IN SALES MANAGEMENT VARSITY COLLEGE | 2010

DIPLOMA IN BUSINESS MANAGEMENT DAMELIN COLLEGE | 2001

□ SKILLS

- Ruby
- Ruby on Rails
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- jQuery

- Bootstrap
- Git & GitHub
- Linux (Ubuntu desktop)
- WordPress
- Using my brain